

District 1, Ho Chi Minh City, Viet Nam

□ (+84) 0822747499 | **■** thinhngow@gmail.com | **☆** https://thinhcorner.com | **⊙** th1nhng0

"We become what we think about"

Summary_

3+ years experience specializing in the frontend development, backend. Super nerd who loves Competitive programming. Interested in devising a better problem-solving method for challenging tasks, and learning new technologies and tools if the need arises.

Technical Skills

Typescript, Javascript, Python, C++, Reactis, Nextis, Threeis, Tailwindcss, Framer Motion, JAMSTACK, Mysql, Mongodb, Agile, Scrum

Work Experience _____

Embery

REMOTE FULLSTACK DEVELOPER

July. 2012 - Now

- Built many websites about ecommerce, landing page.
- Built a 3D experiment website with Threejs
- · Using docker to setup microservices.
- Using agile and scrum workflow.

King Attorney

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

Jan. 2021 - April. 2022 • Built and deployed a information website about law. Using react.js and RESTFul API.

• Built tools to crawl data from internet and import to database with python.

Honors & Awards

NATIONAL

2019 Consolation Prize, National High School Informatics Competition for excellent students.

DOMESTIC

2022 1st Prize, HACKATHON WebDev Adventure 3rd Prize, Student Informatics Olympiad

Education

University of Science - VNUHCM B.S. IN MATHEMATICS AND COMPUTER SCIENCE

Mar. 2010 - Now

GPA 7.5

LEADER

Extracurricular Activity

AI4VN 2022 - VAIPE: Medicine Pill Image Recognition Challenge

• Leader of a team of 5 people

• Learning how to build a deep learning model end-to-end and how to manage a small team.

SEPTEMBER 9, 2022 Ngô Phú Thinh · Résumé

Aug. 2022 - Sep. 2022